I'm really sorry.
我很抱歉
Does he wear glasses or contact lenses?
他戴眼鏡還是隱形眼鏡？
Glasses.
眼鏡
You'll have to hurry up.
你得快點上路了
He decided that his brown leather shoes were the best pair to wear.
他決定還是穿那雙最舒服的棕色皮鞋
His back hurt a little but not like some other times in the past
他的後背有點疼，但是不像有些時候
when the pain was intolerable.
痛得難以忍受
He was thinking his wife didn't love him at all any more.
他覺得，妻子早已不再愛自己了
He didn't burst into tears and he didn't think that the first thing people most people do
他沒有痛哭流涕，也不覺得這種情況下
when they realise someone doesn't love them anymore is cry.
自己理應落淚
Sir, do you mind taking a look into the camera here for me?
先生，請看一下鏡頭好嗎？
That'll do. Thank you.
好了，謝謝您
Have you ever been on your own before?
您以前獨居過嗎？
No, never.
從來沒有
Are you allergic to any foods?
你對什麼食物過敏嗎？
No.
沒有
Your last relationship lasted how many years?
您的上一段感情持續了多長時間？
Around 12.
12年左右吧
Do you remember how long exactly, sir?
您還記得具體有多長嗎，先生？
11 years and one month.
11年零1個月
- Sexual preference? - Women.
- 性取向是？ - 女性
However, I had one homosexual experience in the past,
但是我以前有過一段同性戀經歷
in college.
是大學時候的事了
Is there a bisexual option available?
有沒有雙性戀這個選項？
No, sir, this option is no longer available since about last summer,
沒有，先生，這個選項大概去年夏天就取消了
due to several operational problems.
因為在執行中出了點問題
I'm afraid you have to decide right now if you want to be registered
您現在就得決定，是想登記為
as a homosexual or a heterosexual.
同性戀還是異性戀
I think I should be registered as a heterosexual.
還是異性戀吧
- Any children, sir? - No.
- 您有子女嗎，先生？ - 沒有
And the dog?
那條狗呢？
My brother. He was here a couple of years ago but he didn't make it.
是我哥哥，他幾年前來過這兒，但是沒能成功
You might remember him:
你可能還記得他：
medium build, 48 years old, bald patch, blond hair.
身材中等，48歲，有點謝頂，金色頭髮
I'm afraid not, sir.
我記不得了，先生
OK, I would like you to write your name clearly on this form in capital letters.
好了，請您將姓名用大寫字母清楚的填在這張表上
And sign it, please.
再簽上名字
That will do. Thank you very much.
可以了，非常感謝您
OK, so you are not allowed to use the volleyball or tennis courts.
你不得使用排球場或網球場
These are only for the couples.
雙人運動僅供情侶
You can use facilities for individual sports, such as squash and golf.
你可以使用單人健身設施，比如壁球和高爾夫
You can stay at the hotel for up to 45 days. You'll be staying in a single room.
您最多可以在酒店住45天，我們會安排您入住單人間
If everything goes well and you make it, you'll be moved to a double room.
如果一切順利，您成功找到伴侶，就會安排您入住雙人間
I'm afraid you cannot keep any of your personal belongings.
您不得保留任何私人物品
We will provide everything you need.
我們會滿足您的一切需要
As far as garments, accessories and shoes are concerned.
也會為您提供服裝，配飾以及鞋子
- You can keep this. - Thank you.
- 您可以留著這個 - 謝謝
Shoe size, please?
您的鞋碼多大？
Forty-four and a half.
四十四號半
Forty-four of forty-five? There are no half sizes.
44還是45？這裏沒有半號
If you need a haircut, call reception one day ahead.
如果您需要理髮，請提前一天預約
Smoking is not allowed.
您不得吸煙
That way you'll be able to run for longer during the hunt without getting tired
以保證您在狩獵期間體力充足
and your breath won't smell when you kiss.
並且在接吻的時候口氣清新
Enjoy your stay.
住得愉快
Excuse me, if we need to get a haircut,
不好意思，如果我們需要理髮，
we must call the reception the day before, is that right?
必須得提前一天打給接待處，是吧？
- That's right. - Great.
- 是的 - 好
His room number was 101.
他的房間號是101
A tranquiliser gun was hanging on the wall above his bed.
一把麻醉槍懸掛在床頭上方
On the table were 20 tranquiliser darts, a black plastic watch,
桌子上有20只麻醉針飛鏢，一隻黑色塑料手錶
a pair of sunglasses and a cologne for men.
一副墨鏡和一瓶古龍水
Inside the wardrobe were four identical grey trousers,
衣櫃裏有四條相同的灰色男褲
four identical button-down shirts in white and blue,
四件相同的白藍色的系扣襯衫
a belt, socks, underwear, a blazer,
以及一條腰帶，襪子，內褲，一件運動上衣
a striped tie and a white bathrobe.
一條條紋領帶以及一件白色浴袍
He looked out the window.
他向窗外看去
The unconscious bodies of the captured loners were lying on the wet ground.
被捕獲的流浪者喪失意識的軀體正躺在潮濕的地面上
"Thank God they wear those waterproof ponchos," he thought.
「幸虧他們穿了防水雨披」，他想
Room 195.
195號房
Two loners, two extra days.
捕獲兩個流浪者，延長兩天
Room 272.
272號房
One loner, one extra day.
捕獲一個流浪者，延長一天
Hello. I'm the hotel manager and this gentleman is my partner.
你好，我是酒店經理，這位先生是我的伴侶
We'd like to welcome you.
歡迎您的到來
You're one of the lucky ones.
您很幸運
You have one of our superior rooms, which means you have a view.
您住的是我們的高級房間，可以欣賞到風景
- Did you read the leaflet? - Yes, I did.
- 您讀過宣傳冊了嗎？ - 讀過了
Very good. Now the fact that you'll turn into an animal
很好，雖然酒店規定如果您在居住期間無法愛上一個人
if you fail to fall in love with someone during your stay here
就會被變成一個動物
is not something that should upset you, or get you down.
但是您也不要太喪氣
Just think as an animal you'll have a second chance to find a companion.
想想看，動物也是有找到伴侶的機會的
But even then, you must be careful.
但即使如此，您一定要謹慎
You need to choose a companion that is a similar type of animal to you.
您作為動物選擇的伴侶必須與您種族相似
A wolf and a penguin could never live together,
一匹狼和一隻企鵝永遠無法一起生活
nor could a camel and a hippopotamus.
駱駝與河馬也是如此
That would be absurd.
那樣就太荒唐了
Think about it.
仔細想想
I understand this discussion is a little unpleasant for you.
我明白，談論這些您不會開心
But it is my duty to prepare you psychologically,
但是幫您為可能發生事做好心理準備
for all possible outcomes.
是我的責任
Now, have you thought of what animal you'd like to be if you end up alone?
您想好可能要變成什麼動物了嗎？
- Yes, a lobster. - Why a lobster?
- 想好了，一隻龍蝦 - 有什麼原因嗎？
Because lobsters live for over 100 years,
因為龍蝦的壽命超過一百年
are blue-blooded like aristocrats
體內流淌的是貴族一般的藍色血液
and stay fertile all their lives.
而且一生都不會失去生育能力
I also like the sea very much.
我也很喜歡海
I water-ski and swim quite well, since I was a teenager.
我年輕的時候就很會水滑和游泳了
I must congratulate you. The first thing most people think of is a dog,
恭喜您，人們第一個想到的大多是狗
which is why the world is full of dogs.
所以世界上才有那麼多狗
Very few people choose an unusual animal, which is why they are endangered.
很少有人選擇變成不尋常的動物，所以有很多都瀕臨滅絕
A lobster is an excellent choice.
龍蝦這個選擇很不錯
Could you stand for us, please?
能請您站起來一下嗎？
This is to show you how easy life is when there are two of something
這是為了讓您明白，無論做什麼事
rather than just one.
都是成雙成對的好
We tend to forget that from time to time.
我們有時候會忘記這一點
The handcuff will be removed at the same time tomorrow.
我們明天會為您解開手銬
- It's alright, Bob. - I hope you enjoy your stay with us.
- 沒事的，鮑勃 - 希望您住得愉快
Goodbye.
再見
Have a good day.
過得愉快
Good morning.
早上好
Room 101.
101號房
44 days left.
剩餘44天
Breakfast is served.
早餐已開始供應
Sit where you like.
隨便坐
His first day was one he'd never forget.
他永遠不會忘記他在酒店第一天
Near his table at breakfast sat a young woman with her head tilted back.
早餐期間，他的桌子附近有一個往後仰頭的年輕女人
Later on he would learn that she often got nosebleeds.
後來他瞭解到，她經常流鼻血
Next to her sat her best friend.
她旁邊坐著她最好的朋友
He thanked the waiter who served him his coffee,
他向為自己送上咖啡的服務生道了謝
and thought about his wife for a moment.
想了會兒他的妻子
A woman who seemed to like butter biscuits
一個似乎很喜歡吃奶油餅乾的女人
offered one to a man drinking a Campari and soda for breakfast.
給了一個拿開胃酒和汽水當早餐的男人一塊餅乾
He then looked behind him and saw a woman
他往後看，看到了一個女人
who he would later find out was absolutely heartless.
後來他才知道，這個女人的心無比冰冷
And some others in the couples area,
他還看見了一些坐在情侶區域的人
whom he'd never meet during his stay at the hotel.
他住在酒店的日子裏沒能認識這些人
That morning, he was really hungry.
他那天早上真的很餓
He could have eaten a whole chicken but ate almost nothing.
他本來可以吃掉一整隻雞，但是卻幾乎什麼都沒吃
- Hello.
- 你好
I've decided to go for a walk outside with my new friend.
我準備和我的新朋友去外面散散步
Let me introduce you. This is Robert.
我來介紹一下，這位是羅伯特
He stays in the room next to mine and has a lisp.
他住在我隔壁，有點口吃
Pleased to meet you. I'm staying in room 101.
很高興見到你，我住在101號房
I'm on the same floor. I'm 186.
我也住一層，186號房
- Would you like to join us? - Why not?
- 一起嗎？ - 好啊
One of these days, it's gonna be me on one of those yachts.
總有一天，我也會登上那其中一艘遊艇的
What are those yachts?
那些遊艇是做什麼用的？
It's the final ordeal before letting you go and the hardest one.
那是放你走之前的最後一關，也是最難的一關
15 days of vacation, just a couple, alone.
情侶獨遊15天
- Didn't you read the leaflet? - I did.
- 你沒讀過傳單嗎？ - 讀過
Have you seen John's leg?
你看到約翰的腿了嗎？
No.
沒有
John, would you show your leg?
能給我看看嗎？
Oh, yeah.
是這樣啊
Room 187, day two.
187號房客，入住第二天
Hello, everyone.
大家好
My mother was left on her own when my father fell in love with a woman
我父親愛上別人之後，我母親就一個人生活
who was better at math than she was.
那個女人的數學比我母親好
She had a postgraduate degree, I think, whereas my mother was only a graduate.
她好像有一個研究生學位，我母親只有一個本科學位
I was 19 at the time.
我那時19歲
My mother entered the hotel but didn't make it and was turned into a wolf.
我母親來到了這裏，但是沒能成功，變成了一匹狼
I really missed her.
我很想念她
I found out she'd been moved to a zoo.
我之後瞭解到她被移往了一所動物園
I often went there to see her.
我經常去那兒看她
I'd give her raw meat.
給她生肉吃
I knew that wolves liked raw meat,
我知道狼喜歡吃生肉
but I couldn't figure out which of the wolves was my mother,
但是我不知道哪匹狼是我母親
so I used to give a little bit to each of them.
所以我就每匹狼都給一點
One day, I decided to enter the enclosure
有一天，我決定進到圍欄裏
I really missed her and I wanted a hug.
我真的很想我的母親，也想擁抱她
I climbed the fence and jumped in.
我爬上圍欄，跳了進去
All the wolves charged at once and attacked me,
所有狼一併衝過來，攻擊了我
all but two, who stood motionless.
但是有兩匹狼沒有動
My guess is that one of those two must have been my mother.
我想，我母親肯定是其中之一
The zoo guards got to me quite quickly and took me to the hospital.
動物園守衛很快趕到我身邊，送我去了醫院
Thankfully, I didn't lose my leg, I just have this limp,
感謝上帝，我保住了腿，只是有點跛
which is also my defining characteristic.
跛腳就是我的個人特色
My wife died six days ago.
我的妻子六天前去世了
She was very beautiful and I loved her very much.
她很美，我很愛她
She had a limp too.
她也是個跛子
Thank you, John. You can return to your seat now.
感謝你的發言，約翰，你可以回去坐下了
Let's move on to our next guest.
有請下一位房客
Room 104, day two.
104號房，入住第二天
Hello, everyone.
大家好
This is only my second day here,
我才在這兒住第二天
but already I feel like a member of a wonderful group.
就已經感覺自己已經融入集體了
My defining characteristic is that I have a very beautiful smile.
我的個人特色是我美麗的笑容
♪ Something's gotten hold of my heart
♪我悄然心動
♪ Keeping my soul and my senses apart
♪我魂不守舍
Have you ever danced with anybody?
你跳過舞嗎？
Sorry?
什麼？
Yes.
跳過
What sort of dancing did you do?
你會跳什麼舞？
Just depends on the music.
看放的是什麼歌了
Do you need to sit down?
你要坐下嗎？
- No, no, no, I'm getting ready to dance. - Ah.
- 不不，我正要去跳舞 - 這樣啊
♪ In a time there was peace with no trouble at all
♪我曾安定，了然紛爭
Can I sit here?
我能坐在這兒嗎？
♪ But then you came my way
♪卻遇上了你
Sorry.
不好意思
♪ And a feeling inside shook my heart
♪我心動搖
♪ Made me want you to stay
♪渴望留在你身邊
♪ All of my life
♪我的一生
- Can I sit here? - Of course.
- 我能坐在這兒嗎？ - 當然
Let me introduce you to my best friend.
這位是我最好的朋友
That woman you were talking to has no feelings whatsoever.
你剛才說話的那個女人，她沒有一絲情感
She feels nothing at all.
什麼都感受不到
She's the best hunter in the hotel, silent and very fast.
她是酒店裏最出色的獵人，速度很快還不出聲
She's the women's record holder, 192 captives.
她是女人裏的最高紀錄保持者，一共狩獵了192個流浪者
♪ Changing the grey, changing the blue
♪不再悲傷，不再猶豫
♪ Scarlet for me, scarlet for you
♪我也纏綿，你也纏綿
Would you like to dance?
想去跳舞嗎？
♪ Every day
♪每一天
♪ You touch me and my mind goes astray
♪你的輕觸使我迷途
♪ And baby
♪還有，我親愛的
♪ Something's gotten hold of my hand
♪牽住我的手
♪ Dragging my soul to a beautiful land
♪洗滌我靈魂
♪ Something's gotten into my life
♪走進我的人生
I'm sorry, I've got blood on your shirt.
真對不起，我把血弄到你的襯衫上了
But don't worry, there are many ways to remove bloodstains from clothing.
但別擔心，有很多辦法可以洗乾淨
One way is to rinse the clothes with cold water then rub with sea salt.
有一個是用冷水沖洗衣服，然後用海鹽搓污漬
Another way is to scrub the stains with cotton wool dipped in ammonia.
還有一個是用脫脂棉泡過氨水後用力擦洗污漬
The third way is to mix flour and water into a paste, like toothpaste,
第三種是用麵粉和水，和成像牙膏一樣的麵團
especially if the clothes are delicate or brightly coloured.
要是衣服很柔弱，或者顏色很顯眼的話嗎，這個方法最好用
But just never use warm water on blood, ever.
就是永遠都別用溫水洗衣服
OK.
知道了
♪ But then you, you, you ♪ You
♪但是你啊你
♪ You came my way
♪我遇到了你
♪ But then you came my way
♪遇到了你
♪ And a feeling I know shook my heart
♪我心蕩漾
♪ Made me want you to stay
♪渴望留在你身邊
♪ All of my nights and all of my days
♪永永遠遠
I think I have to rest for a little bit. My leg's hurting.
我覺得我得歇會兒了，腿有點疼
That's OK.
沒關係
Well, let me know when you feel better and we can dance again.
你好點了的話告訴我，我們再接著跳
♪ And my senses apart
♪我情亂神迷
♪ Something has invaded my night
♪夜晚不復沉靜
♪ Painting my sleep with a colour so bright
♪夢鄉如此多彩
♪ Changing the grey
♪不再悲傷
♪ Changing the blue
♪不再憂鬱
♪ Scarlet for me
♪我也纏綿
♪ Scarlet for you
♪你也纏綿
Leave the building in an orderly fashion.
請有序離開
Do hurry up but please be careful.
請盡快，但是務必小心
Nobody needs to get hurt or injured.
小心不要受傷
And good luck with the hunt.
祝各位狩獵好運
I wish I didn't have this limp.
真希望我不是跛子
I used to be very good at running but not any more.
我以前很會跑步，但現在不行了
I'm sure I'll be slower than them.
我肯定沒他們跑得快了
If I were you, I'd think of some tricks that use the element of surprise
我要是你的話，就會想出些出其不意的花招
instead of speed.
而不是光比速度
You're right.
你說得對
That's what I'll do.
我就那麼辦
Room 186. One loner, one extra day.
186號房，捕獲一個流浪者，延長一天
38 days' stay left, plus one, 39.
共39天
Room 180.
180號房
The days of your stay remain unchanged.
剩餘天數不變
Room 290.
290號房
Four loners, four extra days.
捕獲四個流浪者，延長四天
154 days left, plus four, 158.
共158天
Room 101.
101號房
The days of your stay remain unchanged.
剩餘天數不變
32 days left.
剩餘32天
Breakfast is served.
早餐已開始供應
Man eats alone.
當一個男人獨自進餐時
How many darts did you use yesterday?
你昨天用了幾個飛鏢？
12.
12個
Please take off your trousers and sit on the bed.
請脫掉褲子，坐在床上
Can we not do this today? It's awful.
今天能別這樣嗎，太難受了
I know. But I'm afraid we have to do it.
我懂，但是不行
And you have no idea how much it helps you psychologically
這麼做會為你尋找伴侶時
in your search for a partner.
提供極大的幫助
Man eats with woman.
當一個男人與一個女人共同進餐時
Lie down.
躺下
Spread your legs. More.
把腿分開，再開點
- Is your room number 186? - Yes, it is.
- 你的房間號是186嗎 - 是的
I imagine you know that masturbation is not permitted
您應該清楚，酒店不允許
in the rooms or any other area of the hotel.
在任何房間或區域手淫
Yes.
我清楚
And yet it has brought to my attention that you continue to do it.
但是我注意到您一直沒有遵守這個規定
Today you became erect quicker than on other days. That's good.
您今天比以往產生反應都快一點，很好
Please, just a little longer.
求你了，再久一點
Have a good day.
祝您今天愉快
That's awful. Just awful.
沒人性，太沒人性了
Were you looking at a photograph while you were masturbating?
您是看著某張照片自慰的嗎？
Yes.
是的
What did the photograph show?
那張照片上是什麼？
A naked woman on a horse in the country.
一個裸體的女人，在鄉下騎馬
If I were in your shoes, I would not be ogling the naked woman but the horse.
如果我是你，我反倒會去關注那匹馬
I'm sure that the horse was once a weak and cowardly man just like you.
我相信那匹馬曾也是像你一樣軟弱無能的男人
Woman walks alone.
當一個女人獨自行走時
Help.
救命
This is not necessary. Please.
沒必要這麼做，拜託了
- It was an accident. I got carried away. - Please.
- 那是個意外，我當時不清醒 - 請配合
- This is not necessary. - Please place your hand in the toaster.
沒必要這麼做 請把您的手放進麵包機裏
This could be a warning.
這是對您的一次警告
Look, I've been good otherwise, I
我其他方面都表現得很好啊，我…
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Please.
對不起，我錯了，求你了
Please, please, that's hurting.
別這樣，別這樣，太疼了
Woman walks with man.
當一個女人和一個男人共同行走時
What they do, as soon as you enter the room,
你進入那間房間後
is to wash your body and your head really well.
他們就會把你的頭和身體洗得乾乾淨淨的
How do you know?
你怎麼知道的？
My uncle used to know a waiter who worked there.
我叔叔以前認識一個在這兒工作的侍者
No waiters know about the procedure,
侍者不會知道這個過程
they're not allowed inside that room.
他們不能進入那個房間
Nevertheless, they peel off the skin,
總而言之，他們會剝掉你的皮膚
which has become soft due to the water and the soap.
而皮膚用水和肥皂清洗後會變軟
Afterwards, they remove the heart, the eyes and other vital organs of the body
之後，他們會用激光或解剖刀
with a laser or scalpels.
移除你的心臟，眼球還有重要器官
Then the procedure changes according to the animal one has chosen.
然後整個過程會根據你選擇的動物而改變
That makes total sense.
很有道理
I mean, I suppose mammals demand a different kind of work
比如說，變成哺乳動物需要的手術
than fowls, for example.
跟鳥類就不一樣
Exactly.
沒錯
Afterwards they throw the remaining body parts
之後他們會丟掉剩餘的身體部位
into the casks outside the hotel's restaurant
扔進酒店餐廳外面的桶裏
and distribute the blood to the hospitals in the city.
然後把你的血捐給城裏的醫院
Why is that?
為什麼？
The blood is used for surgeries where there are no blood donors available.
沒有獻血者的時候，就用這些血來做手術
- New guests arrived yesterday. - Yes, I saw.
- 昨天有一批新房客到了 - 我看到了
I think I saw a woman with a limp.
我好想看到了一個跛腳的女人
It's just a sprained ankle.
她只是扭傷腳了
She'll be walking normally again in a few days.
過幾天就能正常走路
That's a shame.
可惜了
That is a shame indeed.
確實
One night on the coach, he sat next to the woman who liked butter biscuits.
有一天晚上，他和那個喜歡吃奶油餅乾的女人並排坐在客車上
He gazed out of the window, not looking at anything in particular,
他向車窗外隨意望去
just trying to avoid talking to her.
以免不得不與她說話
- How's Bob? - He's fine.
- 鮑勃怎麼樣了？ - 挺好的
I'd give anything to go for a walk with you and Bob one afternoon.
我特別想跟你和鮑勃找一天下午出去散散步
The dog's not allowed out of the room, I'm afraid.
酒店不可能讓狗離開房間的
"There are some excuses that no one can argue with," he thought.
總有找不出破綻的借口，他這樣想著
Some excuses are without doubt better than others.
毫無疑問，有的借口比其他的要好
And that was a really good one.
而那個借口著實不錯
These biscuits are for Bob.
這些是給鮑勃的餅乾
I want you to give them to him
你想獎勵他的時候
whenever you want to reward him for something.
就可以給它吃
- Tell him they're from me. - Thank you.
- 告訴他是我給的 - 謝謝
Can I come to your room sometime for a chat?
我可以時不時去你的房間聊天嗎？
I could give you a blow-job or you could just fuck me.
我可以幫你吹，或者你可以上我
I always swallow after fellatio and I've got absolutely no problem with anal sex
我不會吐出來，而且肛交也沒問題
if that's your thing.
你要是喜歡的話
My ex-husband always used to say I had the most beautiful thighs he'd ever seen.
我前夫以前總是說，我的大腿是他見過最美的
But let's not talk about him.
但是咱們還是別提他了
My room number is 180, so my telephone extension's 180.
我的房間號是180，電話分機號也是180
Hope I can catch some loners tonight.
真希望我今晚能抓到幾個流浪者
I haven't caught any the last few nights.
我前幾晚一個都沒抓住
Hope you catch lots too.
也希望你能抓到很多
Thank you very much.
非常感謝
If I don't find a suitable partner soon,
如果我不能很快找到一個合適的伴
I'm gonna kill myself by throwing myself out of one of the rooms.
我就要找個房間跳樓自殺
Out of the window.
從窗戶跳下去
I want you to know that.
希望你知道
My room is on the first floor.
我的房間在一層
"I hope I catch some loners today," she said.
她說道「我希望今天自己能抓到幾個流浪者」
"And I hope you catch lots too."
「也希望你能抓到很多」
She then told him that if she didn't find a suitable partner soon,
接著她告訴他，如果她不能很快找到一個合適的伴侶
she was going to kill herself by jumping from one of the room windows,
她就要找個房間從窗戶跳下去自殺
320, maybe, or one higher up.
也許在320號房，或者再高一層
480, that would be even better.
480號房，就更好了
When she stopped talking, he stared at her blankly, not knowing what to say.
她沉默下來後，他茫然地盯著她，一句話也說不出來
He then looked out at the woods
他接著望向樹林
and thought once more how good his excuse had been.
回想著他絕妙的借口
Not bad. Bit higher.
不錯，再高點
Have you thought about what animals you wanna be if you don't make it?
你考慮過如果沒找到伴侶要變成什麼動物了嗎？
A lobster.
龍蝦
I'm gonna be a parrot if I don't make it.
我要變成鸚鵡
Why don't you become parrots too?
要不你們倆也變成鸚鵡吧？
And then we'll all be together.
這樣我們三個就可以在一塊了
You're a complete idiot,
你個蠢蛋
picking one of the few animals that can talk
自己連話都說不清楚
when you have a speech impediment.
偏偏卻選了個能說話的動物
You'll lisp, even as an animal.
你就算變成了動物，口吃的毛病都治不好
As for you, they'll catch you and put you in a pot of boiling water until you die.
至於你，會有人把你抓了丟進鍋裏煮熟了的
And then they'll crack open your claws with a tool, like pliers,
然後用老虎鉗破開你的鉗子
and they'll suck out what little flesh you have with their mouths.
用嘴把你的肉吸出來吃掉
You're pathetic, both of you.
你們兩個真是可悲劇透了
I'm not gonna be turned into some animal.
我不會被變成動物的
I'll come and visit you, though, with my partner,
但是我會跟我的伴侶去看你們的
when we're walking together in some park or when we're swimming in the sea.
等我們去公園裏散步，去海裏游泳
Or when we're on one of our trips.
或者去旅遊的時候見吧
Friends.
別這樣，朋友們
I'm not afraid.
我不怕你
Room 187, please.
187號房客，請上前
It's no coincidence that the targets are shaped like single people and not couples.
酒店把這些靶子做成單身者的形狀，絕非偶然
Hello.
你好啊
- Hello. - Your swimsuit is very nice.
- 你好 - 你的泳衣很好看
Thank,
謝...
- Thank you very much. - You're welcome.
- 謝謝你 - 不客氣
Do you like to swim breaststroke, front crawl, butterfly or backstroke?
你喜歡蛙泳，爬泳，蝶泳還是仰泳？
I like all strokes equally.
擊水的游法我都很喜歡
You know, I love breaststroke.
我很喜歡蛙泳
No, really. My friends often tease me and say,
真的，我的朋友們經常嘲笑我說，
"Stop swimming breaststroke all the time."
「別老是蛙泳了」
And then they laugh.
然後就笑話我
Breaststroke is great. It's excellent exercise for the back.
蛙泳對背部鍛煉很有效
When swimming breaststroke, men shouldn't wear swim shorts,
男人不應該穿著游泳短褲游蛙泳
as it really limits movement in the buttocks.
因為游泳短褲會局限身體動作
- But you knew that, didn't you? - I think your nose is bleeding.
- 你應該已經知道了吧？ - 你流鼻血了
Really?
真的嗎？
Ah, no.
真是的
This happens to me all the time.
我老是這樣
It's really, really annoying.
真的很煩人
I know. I have a nosebleed problem too.
我懂，我也老是流鼻血
I saw what you did. It must have hurt.
我看見你做什麼了，肯定很疼吧
Is it coming out?
流出來了嗎？
No.
沒有
- Yes. - Can I use a tissue?
- 流出來了 - 能給我張餐巾紙嗎？
Yes.
給
I'm gonna ask you a question and I want you to answer me honestly.
我問你個問題，誠實回答我
What's worse: to die of cold and hunger in the woods,
在森林裏冷死餓死
to become an animal that will be killed and eaten by some bigger animal
變成動物然後被更大的動物殺死吃掉
or to have a nosebleed from time to time?
或者偶爾流鼻血，哪個更糟糕一點？
- Exactly. - Mm.
- 沒錯 - 嗯
- She doesn't suspect that you're lying? - No.
- 她沒有懷疑你說謊？ - 沒有
I'm very happy because we have a new couple.
我很開心，因為誕生了一對新伴侶
They met just two days ago but they're very much in love and perfectly suited.
他們兩天前才相遇，但已經十分相愛，並且適合對方
They both have the same problem with their noses, they bleed quite suddenly.
他們兩個都時不時會流鼻血
Tomorrow they'll be transferred to a double room
明天，他們會搬到雙人房裏
with a larger wardrobe and a larger bathroom.
那裏的衣櫃和廁所更大
They will remain in the double room for two weeks,
在雙人房居住兩星期後
and then they'll be transferred to the yachts for a further two weeks.
他們會到遊艇上再生活兩個星期
We wish you every success and we hope you will return to the city as a couple.
我們祝你一切順利，並且以夫妻的身份回到城市裏
- I'm very happy. - Me, too.
- 我很幸福 - 我也是
Congratulations.
恭喜
The course of your relationship will be monitored closely
我們的員工，以及我本人
by our staff and by me personally.
會密切監督你們這段感情的進展
If you encounter any problems, any tensions, any arguing,
如果你們遇到任何無法自行解決的問題或矛盾
that you cannot resolve yourselves, you will be assigned children.
我們會分配你們一個孩子
That usually helps, a lot.
孩子會帶給你們極大的幫助
Good morning, room 101.
101號房，早安
Seven days left.
剩餘7天
Breakfast is served.
早餐已開始供應
You have really nice hair.
你的頭髮很漂亮
I know.
我知道
Look.
看
How do you like mine?
你覺得我的頭髮怎麼樣
Well, I think you have quite dry hair.
嗯，有點干
The colour is OK, though.
但是顏色還不錯
The most important thing is that you're not bald.
主要是你沒有謝頂
However, when it comes to men, baldness is always a possibility you can't avoid.
但是對男人來說，謝頂是難免的
- Is your father bald? - No, he isn't.
- 你父親是謝頂嗎？ - 不是
And even if someday I lose my hair, there are things I can do to get my hair back.
而且即使有一天我開始掉頭髮了，我也可以彌補回來
I can have a hair transplant.
我可以植發
- You can always tell when someone's had a hair transplant. - I know.
- 那個太明顯了 - 我知道
Nice hair is not something you can get. It's something you're born with.
好頭髮是天生的
And the fact that your father isn't bald shouldn't put you at ease.
而且就算你父親不是謝頂，你也不能放鬆警惕
Have you decided what you're going to do on your last day?
你想好了在這兒的最後一天要做什麼了嗎？
I'm still thinking about it.
沒呢
Morning, ladies.
早上好，女士們
So today is your last day.
今天是你的最後一天了
And as is customary, you can choose how you would like to spend your last night.
按照慣例，你可以自由安排你在酒店的最後一晚
What I always say in these situations is,
我通常給出的建議是
it would be wise to choose something you can't do as an animal...
選擇做一些你作為動物無法完成的事情為妙
for example, read a work of classic literature
比如，讀一本經典文學作品
or sing a song you really like.
或者唱一首你很喜歡的歌
It would be silly to choose
反之，選擇去散步
for example a walk in the grounds,
或者與某人性交
or to have sexual intercourse with another person,
就很不明智
because those are things you can do as an animal.
因為這些事情變成動物以後也可以做
But first your best friend has written something she'd like to read to you,
在你決定之前，你最好的朋友想給你讀點東西
which is really very touching.
是她寫給你的話，很感人
"We always sat together at school.
「我們在學校一直坐在一起
And whenever I had a problem, I talked to you about it
我總是跟你傾吐我的煩惱
because you always gave the best advice.
因為你給我的建議最棒
When we didn't manage to find dance partners at the school prom,
當我們找不到舞伴參加學校舞會時
the fact that we were together at that difficult moment gave me strength.
我們在困難時刻的友誼給了我力量
I'm sorry that things have come to this.
我很抱歉，事情發展到了這個地步
I'm sure that if you had a few more days, you would find someone, just like I did,
我相信，再多給你點時間，你也會像我一樣找到某人的
because you're an admirable person,
因為你是個大好人
and you have very beautiful hair and very nice breasts.
而且有一頭美麗的頭髮，和迷人的胸部
I was always jealous of your hair, you know that.
你知道的，我很羨慕你的頭髮
You were, are, and always will be my best friend and I'll think of you often.
你曾經是，現在是，而且永遠都會是我最好的朋友，我會常常想起你的
And I'll always wear those silver earrings you gave me for my birthday.
而且我會一直戴著我過生日時你送給我的銀耳環
I'll miss you.
我會想念你的
And however many new girlfriends I make in a few days when I move back into the city,
而且不管我搬回城裏後認識多少新女朋友
I don't think I'll find another as true."
都不會再遇到像你...」
I'd like to watch the film Stand By Me,
我想一個人看部電影
with River Phoenix, Kiefer Sutherland and Richard Dreyfus. Alone.
瑞凡·菲尼克斯，基弗·薩瑟蘭和理查德·德雷弗斯演的《伴我同行》
Excellent choice.
很好
Lovely film.
那部電影很好看
Please leave a message.
請留言
Hello. You're probably in the bathroom,
你好，估計你正在浴室裏
that's why you can't hear the phone ring.
所以聽不到電話鈴
Nothing like a cold shower in the morning.
早上衝個涼水澡最好了
Well, I'll call you a little bit later, after you've finished your shower.
我等你洗完澡再打給你
We'll talk later.
待會兒再聊
Bye.
再見
One day, as he was playing golf,
有一天在他打高爾夫球的時候
he thought that it is more difficult to pretend
他想，比起裝作沒有感情
that you do have feelings when you don't
還是裝作有感情
than to pretend you don't have feelings when you do.
更難一點
He also thought that he liked her accent,
他又想到，自己很喜歡她的口音
and he'd always preferred women with short hair.
而且自己更喜歡短頭髮的女人
So he decided that she was the one.
所以他決定是她了
During the hunt, he would follow her,
他在狩獵時候跟著她
and as soon as she shot a loner, he would say to her,
而且每當她打到流浪者的時候，他會說
"I wish we had real guns instead of these silly tranquiliser ones.
「真希望我們能用真槍，而不是這些沒用的麻醉槍
Why don't you kill him with your bare hands?"
你應該空手殺死他」
And the moment she puts her hands around the loner's throat, he would say,
然後當她把手放在流浪者的脖子上時，他就說
"I hope he dies right away."
「真希望他馬上死掉」
Did anyone see what happened?
有人看到出什麼事了嗎？
What happened?
出什麼事了？
She jumped from the window of room 180.
她從180號房間的窗戶跳下去了
There's blood and biscuits everywhere.
到處都是血和餅乾
I hope she dies right away.
真希望她立馬死掉
On second thoughts
但是另一方面
I hope she suffers quite a bit before she dies.
讓她痛苦一會兒再死也不錯
I just hope her pathetic screams can't be heard from my room.
我只希望她的慘叫聲別傳到我的房間裏
Because I was thinking about having a lie-down and I need peace and quiet.
我打算安安靜靜地休息一會兒
I was playing golf and I'm quite tired.
我剛才去打高爾夫了，有點累
The last thing I need is some woman dying slowly and loudly.
窗外有個又吵又鬧的垂死女人可不好
I can't hear you with all this screaming.
太吵了，我聽不清你在說什麼
We'll talk some other time when it's quieter.
我們下次找個安靜的地方再聊
Goodbye.
再見
One message.
一條留言
Hello. You're probably in the bathroom,
你好，估計你正在浴室裏
that's why you can't hear the phone ring.
所以聽不見電話鈴
Nothing like a cold shower in the morning.
早上衝個涼水澡最好了
Well, I'll call you a little bit later, after you've finished your shower.
我等你洗完澡再打給你
We'll talk later.
待會兒再聊
Bye.
再見
Mind if I join you?
介意我跟你一起嗎？
Martini?
馬提尼啊？
I think we are a match.
我覺得我們很合適
Yes, I think so too.
我也這麼覺得
The keys to the double room, please.
麻煩給我雙人房的鑰匙
I wish you the best of luck. We all wish you the best of luck.
祝你們好運，我們都祝你們好運
Do you normally sleep on the left side of the bed or the right?
你平時睡在床左邊還是右邊？
- The right. You? - The left.
- 右邊，你呢？ - 左邊
Perfect.
正好
Spread your legs.
別蜷著腿
Should I turn off the light or would you like to read?
我是現在關燈，還是你想再看會兒書？
I'd like to read. Does the light bother you?
我想再看會兒書，會打擾到你嗎？
No.
不會
I'm not bothered by light or noise.
開著燈有噪音我都能睡得著
I'm a deep sleeper.
我睡覺很沉
- Hello.
- 你們好
Congratulations.
恭喜
- Thank you. - This is our new daughter.
- 謝謝 - 這是我們的新女兒
Her name's Elizabeth.
伊麗莎白
Elizabeth, give the nice man a kiss. He's a friend of mine.
伊麗莎白，親吻一下這位善良的男士，他是我的朋友
The last thing I want right now is a kiss from a silly little girl.
我才不要讓一個傻乎乎的小女孩親我
Come on, move away.
過來吧
Don't cry, Elizabeth, you should thank me.
別哭了，伊麗莎白，你應該謝謝我
Now you'll have a limp and be more like your father.
現在你也像你父親一樣跛腳了
What was that sound?
什麼聲音？
Did you say something?
你說話了嗎？
No.
沒有
Do you mind if we fuck in a position where I can see your face?
介意咱們換個姿勢嗎，我想看到你的臉
Sure.
可以
Turn the light on please, so I can see you better.
把燈打開吧，我想看清楚你
Good morning.
早上好
I killed your brother.
我把你的哥哥殺了
I left him to die very slowly.
我讓他死得很慢
He may not be dead yet even as we speak.
他現在可能還沒死乾淨呢
I was kicking him for ages.
我踢了他很久
Doesn't matter.
沒關係
He whined a little, a strange kind of bark.
他哀嚎了一會兒，叫聲很奇怪
Something like this.
有點像這樣
It must have been from the pain.
一定是疼得
- You didn't hear anything? - No.
- 你什麼都沒聽到？ - 沒有
You really are a deep sleeper.
你真的睡得很沉
- Would you like some coffee? - I'd love some.
- 你想喝咖啡嗎? - 當然
As soon as I wash my face and brush my teeth, though.
但是我得先洗臉刷牙
I can't wait to hear the story you promised to tell me last night,
我等不及想聽你昨晚說好要給我講的故事了
about that student of yours at the university
關於你在大學裏的學生
and his awful final project.
還有他那個糟糕的期末作業的故事
It's really a very funny story.
那件事確實很好笑
His name was Ryess -
他的名字是瑞斯——
R-Y-E-S-S. Ryess.
日-無-誒-斯，瑞斯
These aren't tears, it's just water. I just washed my face.
我沒有流眼淚，只不過是我剛洗了臉
I knew you were lying. I can't understand why you did it,
我知道你在說謊，
when you know as well as anyone that a relationship cannot be built on a lie.
你應該知道感情不能建立在謊言上，所以我不理解你為什麼要說謊
We're going to the hotel manager right now and you'll get the punishment you deserve.
我們現在就去找酒店經理，然後讓你接受應有的懲罰
What's the punishment for this?
什麼懲罰？
They turn you into the animal no one wants to be.
他們會把你變成沒人想當的動物
I saw your partner running back that way.
我看到您的伴侶朝著那邊跑去了
He looked frantic.
他好像很慌亂
Is everything OK?
一切都還好嗎？
At first he wanted to kill her in some horrible and painful way,
他本來想以某種可怕又痛苦的方式殺死她
like the death she had inflicted on his brother.
就像她對他哥哥做的那樣
Take her legs, please.
麻煩抬著她的腿
He thought about kicking her in the stomach over and over again,
他想著一次又一次踢她的肚子
and then stabbing her in the same spot in the stomach.
然後在同一個位置刺上一刀
But then he thought there wouldn't be much point,
但是他又想到，那麼做沒什麼意義
because she was already unconscious
因為她已經沒有意識了
and wouldn't feel any pain from the kicks, or the knife.
因此被踢幾腳，刺上一刀也不會感覺到任何痛苦
You have to shoot me so they won't suspect I helped you.
你得拿麻醉槍射我，不然他們會懷疑我幫了你的
A hotel maid helped him.
一個酒店女僕幫了他
He couldn't understand why she did it.
他不理解為什麼她要這麼做
So he decided to turn her into an animal.
他決定把她變成動物
He dragged her to the room where the transformations took place.
他把她拉進變形房間
I asked him many times what sort of animal he turned her into,
我問過他很多次，他把她變成了什麼動物
but he always gave me the same answer:
但是他給我的答案永遠一樣：
"That's none of your concern."
「你不用管」
That night, he left the hotel once and for all.
那天晚上，他永遠的離開了酒店
He began to run without knowing where he was headed.
他開始盲目的逃跑
But he was headed towards us.
但是他跑向了我們
This was the start of his new life.
這就是他新生活的開始
And back then, he didn't know how much it hurts to be alone,
那時候，他還不知道單身一人有多麼痛苦
how much it hurts when you cannot reach to rub pain-relief ointment on your back,
不能自己給背上抹止痛膏時有多麼痛苦
and you are constantly in pain.
而且這種疼痛是持之以恆的
I found him in the woods.
我在樹林裏找到了他
He escaped from the hotel.
他從酒店逃出來了
Are you a doctor, by any chance?
你也許是個醫生？
- No. - That's a pity.
- 不是 - 可惜了
We need a doctor around.
我們這兒需要個醫生
We had one, but they caught him a couple of months ago.
本來有一個，但是幾個月前被抓走了
I'm an architect.
我是建築師
That's OK.
挺好
So, welcome.
那麼，歡迎你
You can stay with us for as long as you like.
你可以無限期和我們呆在一起，
You can be a loner until the day you die. There is no time limit.
你這輩子都可以當一個流浪者，沒有時間期限
Thank you very much.
很感謝你
By the way,
還有
any romantic or sexual relations between loners are not permitted.
流浪者之間不允許存在情侶或者性伴侶關係
And any such acts are punished.
如果有此類行為，你會遭到懲罰
Is that clear?
清楚了嗎？
Can I have a conversation with someone?
我可以和別人說話嗎？
Of course you can.
當然可以
So as long as there is no flirting or anything like that.
只要沒有調情之類的行為就可以
That applies to dance nights as well.
跳舞的時候也一樣
We all dance by ourselves, that's why we only play electronic music.
我們都自己跳舞，所以我們只播放電子音樂
What happened to your mouth?
你的嘴怎麼了？
He can't speak. He was given the Red Kiss.
他不能講話，我們給他做了血吻
What's the Red Kiss?
血吻是什麼？
We slashed his lips with a razor and the lips of another loner,
用激光切掉了他和另一個流浪者的嘴唇
and we forced them to kiss each other.
然後我們強迫他們親吻對方
That was a couple of days ago now.
那是幾天前的事了
But the cuts were deep and they're still in pain. They were flirting, you know.
但是傷口很深，所以他們還是很疼，他們調情了
Some punishments are worse than other punishments.
有的懲罰比其他懲罰嚴重一些
Having your thumb cut is worse than having your head shaved.
切掉手指比剃光頭髮糟糕
And having a hot boiled egg under your armpit
在腋窩下放煮熟的雞蛋
is worse than having your leg kicked.
比讓別人踢你的腿糟糕
The punishment I am afraid of isn't the Red Kiss but another one,
我最害怕的懲罰不是血吻，而是另一個
that is called the Red Intercourse.
叫做血交
I have never seen it happen, but it's not difficult to imagine what it means.
我從來沒見過執行過程，但是不難想像
Oh, my God, I am so afraid of it.
我的天，我太害怕了
Move.
移動
Hide.
躲藏
That was the first time I saw him.
那是我第一次見到他
He was hiding behind a tree close to mine.
他躲在離我不遠的一棵樹後面
He seemed quite presentable.
他看上去很體面
The next day, in the city,
第二天，在城裏
he found out that I was short-sighted too.
他瞭解到我也是近視眼
That night in my sleep,
那天晚上
I dreamt that we lived in a big house together in the city,
我夢到我們一起住在城裏的一座大房子裏
with a large well-lit kitchen,
房子裏有漂亮的廚房
and I was wearing dark blue trousers and a tight cream blouse.
我穿著深藍色的褲子，和奶油色緊身襯衫
And he took my clothes off and fucked me up the arse.
然後他脫掉我的衣服，從後面操我
And as he was fucking me, a thug came into the kitchen,
與此同時，一個惡棍闖進了廚房
and took the steak knives from the second draw and attacked us,
然後從第二層抽屜抽出了一把牛排刀，攻擊了我們
stabbing the knives into our bellies one by one.
一下接一下，用刀捅我們的肚子
I woke up terrified.
我驚恐的醒過來
Try harder.
再努點力
Don't give up. You know you should have been more careful.
別放棄，你知道自己應該謹慎一點的
Try harder or they'll find you and you'll be turned into an animal - a weak one.
再努力一把，不然他們找到你，把你變成動物，還是小動物
We must get a move on now. It's really too dangerous to stay here.
我們得走了，待在這兒太危險了
If you manage to free yourself, run as fast as you can and come find us.
如果你掙脫了，盡全力快跑然後找到我們
If you manage to free yourself but think you'll die from the bleeding,
但就算你掙脫了，估計也會失血而死
go straight to your grave.
直接走向自己的墳墓
Have you dug your own grave?
你給自己挖好墳墓了嗎？
Yes.
挖好了
Very good.
很好
That's enough for now.
就這樣
I'm going to go hunting for truffles.
我要去挖點松露
They're delicious and quite rare. A kilo can fetch a lot of money.
松露很好吃，又很稀有，挖兩斤可以賺到很多錢
You're going to need a pig. They're impossible to find otherwise.
你得帶一頭豬，要不然挖不到的
- I know. - Don't be long.
- 我知道 - 別走太久
- Gotta get them back in 50 minutes. - OK.
- 五十分鐘後就回來 - 好
Hello, David.
你好，大衛
Hello, Robert.
你好，羅伯塔
What you did to that woman was dreadful.
你對那個女人做的事太可怕了
She killed my brother.
她殺了我哥哥
I would have done the same thing if she'd killed you.
她殺的要是你，我也會那麼做
You're like a brother to me. Oh, you're my best friend in the whole world.
你就像我的兄弟一樣，你是我全世界最好的朋友
I don't think I'm your best friend in the whole world.
我可不覺得我是你全世界最好的朋友
You used to spend much more time with John.
你以前跟約翰呆在一起的時間更多
Oh, who's John?
誰是約翰啊？
- John, the Limping Man. - Oh, yeah.
- 約翰，那個跛腳的 - 他啊
I didn't even remember his name.
我都不記得他叫什麼了
Or his face.
也不記得他長什麼樣了
You're the one I think of whenever I need a friend.
你才是我需要時第一個想到的朋友
Nevertheless, did John make it?
話說回來，約翰成功了嗎？
They're getting ready for the yacht.
他們正準備上遊艇
It all begins this week.
這周就開始
Everyone says they're gonna make it as they're perfectly suited
所有人都說他們可以做到，因為他們很適合對方
and the child will help them get past the fighting and arguing.
而且他們領養的孩子能幫他們度過爭吵
- That's great. - You're not thinking about coming back?
真不錯 你不考慮回來嗎？
You know, if you told the hotel manager about your brother,
如果你告訴酒店經理你哥哥的事
she'd probably forgive you.
說不定她會原諒你
No, it's really nice to be on your own.
不了，我自己一個人挺好
There's no one tying you down.
在這裏不會被綁起來
You listen to music whenever you like, you masturbate whenever you want,
隨便聽音樂，隨便自慰
go for walks whenever you like,
隨便去散步
have a chat whenever you like.
隨便聊聊天
I don't miss companionship at all.
我一點都不想念有人陪伴
I just miss you, 'cause you were my one true friend.
我就是很想你，因為你是我唯一真正的朋友
Are you gonna shoot me?
你會開槍射我嗎？
I'm afraid so.
恐怕會
I only have two days left.
我只剩兩天了
What did you say? I can't understand the way you speak.
你說什麼？我聽不懂你說話
I'm going to shoot you. I only have two days left, I need more time.
我會開槍射你，我只剩兩天了，我需要時間
Do you actually believe another day will make a difference?
你真的相信再多一天能有什麼不同嗎？
Have you seen how ugly you are?
你照過鏡子嗎？
You haven't got a chance. If I was a woman...
你一點機會都沒有，如果我是女人...
Don't tell anyone I helped you.
別告訴任何人我幫了你
If you want to repay me, there is a way.
你要是想報答我，就這麼辦
If you kill a rabbit, bring it to me to eat.
如果你殺死一隻兔子，就帶給我吃
Do you promise?
保證嗎？
- Yes. - Bye.
- 保證 - 再見
Bye.
再見
You carefully flay the rabbit with a sharp knife and cut off its head.
你得用鋒利的刀小心的剝了兔子皮，切掉腦袋
You then slice open its belly and stuff it with well-washed red and green peppers,
劃開它的肚子，給裏塞滿洗乾淨的紅椒青椒
not too spicy, and a little garlic and mint.
不要太辣，再加點大蒜和薄荷
You then soak it in lemon juice and leave it a while to marinate the flesh
然後放進檸檬汁裏，醃一會兒
before you skewer it on a stick and roast it over the fire for about an hour.
然後就可以把兔肉叉在棍子上，放火上烤一個小時左右
That's my favourite food,
兔肉
rabbit.
是我最喜歡的食物
Woman, brunette, 50 years old.
女性，棕髮，50歲左右
Marriage certificate expired two months ago.
結婚證明於兩個月前過期
My husband's away on a business trip.
我丈夫出差了
Yeah, OK. Can I have a look?
好，介意我檢查一下嗎？
Hands.
伸手
No dirt under her nails or mud on her shoes.
指甲裏和鞋上都沒有泥土
9 Belsize Road.
貝爾賽路九號
- So your husband is away? - Yes.
- 你的丈夫不在？ - 是的
Where?
他在哪兒？
Good morning, sir. Are you here alone?
早上好，先生，你一個人嗎？
Good morning, Officer.
你好，長官
No, I'm here with my partner.
我是和我伴侶來的
She's inside one of the stores, shopping right now.
她在去商店買東西了
Can I see your certificate, please?
我能看一下你的結婚證明嗎？
My partner keeps it in her purse.
在我的伴侶的包裏
You see, I am losing it all the time.
因為我經常丟三落四
I see.
明白
And what store is she shopping in?
她在哪家店買東西？
Oh, here she is.
她來了
I'm sorry, darling.
真對不起，親愛的
They had such a huge variety of pain-relief ointment.
他們那兒的止痛藥太多了
I bought you this one. I hope it's the one you were looking for.
我給你買了這種，希望是你想要的那個
That's wonderful, dear.
太好了，親愛的
Can I have my certificate, please?
能拿一下我的結婚證明嗎？
Of course, darling. Would you like to see mine also, Officer?
當然了，我的用看一下嗎，長官？
No, that's OK.
不必了
Thank you, sir.
謝謝你的配合，先生
- You have a good day. - Thank you, Officer. You have a good day.
祝你愉快 謝謝你，長官，也祝你愉快
- Madam. - Sir.
- 女士，再見 - 再見
If I'm walking too slowly, just say, and I'll pick up my pace.
我要是走得太慢了，就告訴我，我可以走快點
This pace is fine.
這樣正好
Maybe don't squeeze my hand so tightly, my palm's getting a little sweaty.
手可不可以松一點，我掌心開始出汗了
- Better? - Yes.
- 這樣好點嗎？ - 嗯
Much better.
好多了
Are you planning on buying anything else nice for yourself while we're here?
既然來城裏了，你有什麼想給自己買的嗎？
Yes, contact lens solution and a Parker Rollerball.
我想買隱形眼鏡護理液，還有派克寶珠筆
I didn't know you were short-sighted.
你也近視啊
I'm short-sighted too.
我也是
Will you stay a few days?
你準備多待幾天嗎？
I'm afraid not, Papa.
不了，爸爸
We're heading back again today.
我們今天就回去
Tomorrow I'm going away on a business trip.
我明天要去出差
You know how demanding my job is.
你也知道我的工作有多累人
Don't ask if I can stay a few days every time I come.
所以別每次我來的時候都問一遍了
Do you all work for the same company?
你們是同事嗎？
- Yes.
- 是
My daughter says me it's a very fine company.
我女兒說那家公司很不錯
Do you agree?
你們覺得呢？
- It's a rather good company. - It is.
- 確實是家很不錯的公司 - 確實
- One of the best, I'd say. - Mm.
- 要我說，是數一數二的 - 嗯
The only problem with the job
唯一的不足
is that I don't have enough time for my wife and kids.
就是沒時間陪我的妻子和孩子
We have four beautiful children.
我們有四個漂亮的孩子
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
- 恭喜你們 - 謝謝
Thank you.
謝謝你
But even if we'd never had children,
但就算我們沒有孩子
I would never dream of leaving my wife.
我也不可能離開我的妻子
Even if it was just the two of us, on our own,
就算只有我們兩個人
we'd go on trips.
我們就去旅遊
We'd go to Portofino in Italy or go to a Greek island for the summer.
我們到了夏天可以去意大利的波多菲諾，或者希臘島
And so our relationship would be as intense as it was at the start.
而且我們倆還會像開始一樣充滿激情
I love my wife so much
我很愛我的妻子
I could die for her.
我願意為她去死
That's how much I love her.
我就是這麼愛她
For your first day in the city, you did great.
鑒於你是第一次來城裏，你表現得還不錯
That part about holiday destinations in the Mediterranean was brilliant.
去地中海度假那段發揮得很棒
Thank you very much.
多謝
When did you become short-sighted?
你什麼時候開始近視的？
When I was 16.
我16歲的時候
You?
你呢？
When I was 12.
12歲
What was the make of your first pair of glasses?
你第一副眼鏡是什麼樣的？
I don't remember.
我不記得了
- Do you have astigmatism too? - Yes.
- 你有散光嗎？ - 有
Would you like me to rub some balm on your back
要我幫你抹藥嗎？
on the bits you can't reach on your own?
就是你自己夠不到的那部分
I'd like that.
好啊
Here?
這兒嗎？
A little lower, please.
再低一點
- Here? - Yes.
- 這兒？ - 對
"Hello, everyone, and good luck.
「大家好，祝你們好運
The room numbers are as follows:
房間號分別為：
room 306, the hotel manager and her partner.
306號：酒店經理和她的伴侶
They both,
他們兩個
they both have nice voices.
聲音都很好聽
Room 240: couple who both love to ski.
240號：一對滑雪愛好者
Room 282: couple who both studied social sciences.
282號：兩人曾研究過社會科學
Name of yacht Bliss: couple prone to nosebleeds."
「天祐號」遊艇：一對愛流鼻血的情侶」
You and you take 306.
你們倆負責306號
You and you take 240.
你們倆負責240號
You take 282.
你負責282號
And you two, take the yacht.
你們倆，負責遊艇
Can I go to the yacht?
我能負責遊艇嗎？
OK, then, so you take the yacht.
那好吧，那你負責遊艇
And you take 282.
你負責282號
And us three, we'll take the manager's room.
咱們三個，負責經理的房間
We have 40 minutes.
我們有40分鐘
You need to speak with the manager.
你得跟經理談
Wake up.
醒醒
Get up.
起來
Sit in that seat over there.
坐到那邊的椅子上
Put your hand behind your back.
手背後
A basketball weighs between 550 and 650 grams.
一隻籃球大概有500到560克重
- Did you know that? - No, I didn't know that.
- 你知道嗎？ - 不，我不知道
Yes.
就是那樣
The weight's different for men's and women's games,
男女比賽的重量不同
but that's roughly how much it weighs.
但是都差不多在這個範圍之間
Do you know how much a volleyball weighs?
你知道一個排球有多重嗎？
No, but I'd like to find out.
不知道，但是我很想知道
- Good evening.
- 晚上好
I have something to tell you.
我有點事想告訴你
His nose doesn't really bleed on its own.
他本來不流鼻血
He bangs it against a wall or a piece of hard wood, or something like that.
他趁你不注意的時候，會用牆或者硬木撞鼻子
Or he cuts it with a penknife when you're not looking.
或者乾脆用小刀劃
You two are not suited.
你們倆並不般配
Shut up. Dad, tell him to leave. I'm sleepy.
閉嘴，爸爸，讓他走開，我困了
And, and I'm quite sure that stain on his T-shirt isn't blood,
而且他T恤上的污漬不是血跡
but cherry juice or tomato ketchup
是櫻桃汁，或者番茄醬
or red watercolour paint or something like that.
或者水彩顏料之類的東西
Or beetroot juice.
也可能是甜菜汁
Do you love her?
你愛他嗎？
With all my heart.
全心全意
How much do you love her, on a scale of 1 to 15?
從1到15，你有多愛他？
14 is a very impressive score.
14很高
He loves her very much indeed.
他確實很愛她
Who do you think we should kill?
你覺得我們應該殺了誰？
Who will be able to live on their own better?
誰更適合一個人生活？
Here's a knife, Mum. Kill him.
這兒有刀，媽媽，殺了他
You'd better get out while you still can.
你最好趁著現在趕緊離開
OK.
好
That's all I came to say, anyway.
反正我來就是想說這些
You.
你
If this woman dies, d'you think you'll manage on your own?
如果這個女人死了，你覺得你會一個人活得下去
Or will you get involved with someone else?
還是會另尋別戀？
No.
不
I can live alone, she can't.
我可以一個人過，她不行
I'm on my own for hours when she's running the hotel.
她忙工作的時候，我可以自己待好幾個小時
I like sitting in the room.
我喜歡一個人坐在房間裏
It relaxes me, calms me.
這樣我很放鬆，很平靜
I like it a lot.
我很喜歡一個人待著
I can definitely live on my own.
我絕對可以一個人生活
Be quiet.
安靜
Take it.
拿著
Shoot her.
殺了她
No.
不
No, no.
不，不
No, God, no.
不，天哪，不要
I'm going to fucking kill your arse.
我要殺了你個混蛋
Don't you fucking care?
你他媽都不在乎我？
Where were you?
你去哪兒了？
I was looking for you.
我剛剛在找你
I was masturbating behind those trees over there.
我剛才去樹後面自慰了
Why aren't you dancing?
你為什麼沒跳舞？
My leg's a little sore.
我腿有點酸
Did you dig your grave?
你給自己挖好墳了嗎？
Not yet.
還沒
I don't mean to pressure you,
我不是想給你施加壓力
or to ruin the mood now that we're celebrating,
或者毀掉慶祝的氣氛
but at some point you'll have to do it.
但是你早晚都得挖
Don't expect anyone else to dig your grave for you or to carry your corpse.
不要指望著別人替你挖，或者扛著你的屍體
We'll throw some dirt over you but that's about it.
我們頂多會往屍體上撒點土
Tomorrow find a spot you like,
明天找一個你喜歡的地方
where the ground isn't too rocky, and make a start.
最好平坦一點，就開始吧
- Enjoy the rest of your evening. - Thank you.
- 祝你今晚愉快 - 謝謝
As soon as his last patient left, I entered his office and I said to him,
最後一名患者離開後，我走進他辦公室，對他說
"Honey, the dinner's ready. However, I'm not sure I can eat right now.
「親愛的，晚餐準備好了，但我現在恐怕吃不了
One of my front teeth hurts a lot.
我有一顆門牙很疼
Can you take a look please, dear?"
你能幫我看看嗎，親愛的？」
"Yes, sure, no problem," he said.
他說，當然了，沒問題
And the minute he turned his head, I took the drill and I shoved it into his chest.
然後在他轉過頭的一瞬間，我拿起鑽頭插進了他的胸膛
That story sounds really interesting but I have to leave.
這個故事很有意思，但是我得走了
I just remembered I left some batteries next to a tree down there.
我剛想起來，我留了幾個電池在那棵樹旁邊
And the last thing I want is to lose them. Sorry.
可不想弄丟了，失陪
Did you catch rabbits?
你抓到兔子了嗎？
- No, someone brought me them. - Who?
- 沒有，但是有人給我帶了 - 誰？
A friend of mine.
我的一個朋友
- Do you want one? - No.
- 你想來點嗎？？ - 不了
You don't need to accept rabbits from other people.
你不要拿別人的兔子
If you need more rabbits, just ask, and I'll bring you more.
你要想吃，問我就是了，我給你多帶一點
Catching a rabbit is difficult, but I'll try to do better.
抓兔子很難，但是我會盡力的
There's no need for you to be indebted to the others.
你不必去欠別人的
Thank you very much.
很感謝你
The man who brought you the rabbits,
給你帶兔子的那個男人
is he short-sighted?
他近視嗎？
I don't know. I don't think so.
我不清楚，應該不是吧
OK.
知道了
Is that a sparrow up in that tree?
那棵樹上是有只麻雀嗎？
I can't really see that far.
那麼遠，我看不太清
But I don't think so.
但應該不是
- Are you short-sighted? - No.
- 你近視嗎？ - 不
You're lying.
你在說謊
It's the truth.
這是事實
What does it say here?
這上面寫著什麼？
YKK.
YKK
You knew that already. All zips say the same thing.
你看之前就已經知道了，拉鏈上寫的字都一樣
I'm not short-sighted.
我不近視
I don't understand why you won't believe me.
你為什麼不相信我
I can see really clearly. I used to be a pilot.
我看東西很清楚，我以前是個飛行員
You're wearing contact lenses.
你戴著隱形眼鏡呢
I don't wear contact lenses. I'm not short-sighted, I swear.
我不戴隱形眼鏡，我真的不近視
You are. You think I'm an idiot and can't tell.
你就是 你覺得我傻到看不出來
Let me see.
讓我看看
Let me see. I want to see your eyes.
讓我看看，我要看你的眼睛
Look up.
往上看
Up, up.
往上，上
Look down now.
再往下看
Look left.
往左
Look right.
往右
Up again.
再往上看
I'm sorry.
對不起
I thought you were trying to fool me.
我還以為你在騙我
For this synchronisation exercise, we have to fully concentrate,
這個同步練習我們倆一定要全神貫注
as we both have to press "play" at exactly the same time.
要同時按下播放鍵
Why don't we just use one headset?
我們用一副耳機不就行了？
Because that's the whole point.
那就沒有意義了
This is an exercise for us.
這是對我們的默契練習
We have to be totally synchronised.
我們必須得練到完全同步
OK.
好
- I'm ready. - OK.
- 我準備好了 - 好
Five, four, three,
五，四，三
two,
二
♪ Where The Wild Roses Grow
♪野玫瑰，何處開
♪ If I show you the roses will you follow?
♪若我予你玫瑰，你是否跟隨我
♪ They call me the Wild Rose
♪世人喚我野玫瑰
♪ But my name is Elisa Day
♪然我名為麗莎黛
We've developed a code so that we can communicate with each other,
我們發明了一套暗語，以方便互相交流
even in front of the others, without them knowing what we are saying.
即使在別人面前，他們也不知道我們在說什麼
When we turn our heads to the left, it means,
頭轉向左邊的時候，意思就是
"I love you more than anything in the world."
「我愛你勝過全世界」
And when we turn our heads to the right, it means,
往右轉，就是
"Watch out, we're in danger."
「小心，有危險」
We had to be very careful in the beginning not to mix up
剛開始，我們得很小心才不會
"I love you more than anything in the world" with "Watch out, we're in danger."
把兩者搞混
When we raise our left arm, it means,
舉起左臂，意思是
"I want to dance in your arms."
我想在你懷裏跳舞
When we make a fist and put it behind our backs, it means,
舉起拳頭放到背後，就是
"Let's fuck."
「我們做吧」
The code grew and grew as time went by.
隨著時間過去，這套暗語越來越完善
And within a few weeks, we could talk about almost anything
過了幾星期，我們基本上不用張嘴
without even opening our mouths.
就什麼都可以說了
Stop it.
停下
That's enough. Show my parents some respect.
- 夠了 - 對我父母尊重點
They are playing you music.
他們在為你們演奏
- That's OK. - No, Mother, it is not OK.
- 沒關係的 - 不，母親，有關係
Please continue.
請繼續吧
Do you want us to perform the same piece or something else?
是想繼續聽這首還是換點別的？
Something else.
換一首吧
Didn't her parents play beautifully?
她父母演奏得真好
Yes, they did.
確實
It was wonderful.
非常動聽
We love each other and we suit each other.
我們彼此相愛，又十分相配
And that's the reason why we've decided to leave the woods
因此，我們決定離開樹林
and stay together forever in the city.
然後在城裏相守一生
Tomorrow during the hunt,
明天狩獵的時候
we're going to disappear and everyone will think we've been captured,
我們會一起失蹤，然後所有人都會以為我們被抓到了
and that we're going to be turned into dogs or canaries or something.
被變成狗或金絲雀之類的了
I think the first thing I'm going to do
我到了城裏
when I get into the city is buy a bathrobe.
要做的第一件事，就是買一件浴袍
And then we'll go to a pool with a high diving board, perfect for diving.
然後我們去一家有很高跳水板的，適合跳水的游泳池
"And we'll do lots of different things together,
「然後我們一起做很多很多事
serious things, not silly ones,
正經的事，不是什麼蠢事
like go for walks in the park or play the guitar together."
比如去公園散步，或者一起彈吉他」
"Portofino. Italian fishing village and upmarket resort,
「波多菲諾，意大利捕魚村莊和高端度假勝地」
famous for its picturesque harbour.
那裏以優美如畫的海港聞名
Population: 439.
人口總數：439人
Beaches nearby:
附近的海灘有：
Paraggi Beach, Camogli, Chiavari and Lavagna.
派拉吉海灘，卡吉莫，奇亞瓦力和拉瓦尼亞海灘
Serifos: Greek island located in the western Cyclades."
塞利福斯島是基克拉底群島西部的希臘島嶼
Can you imagine why I brought you to such a quiet place today?
你知道我今天為什麼帶你來這麼僻靜的地方嗎？
No.
不知道
Because I think it's the perfect spot for your grave.
因為我覺得你的墳墓挖在這兒正合適
Now cover yourself with soil.
用土把自己蓋起來
Use you hands.
用手弄
Over your face too.
臉也蓋上
You wouldn't want your face to get eaten by dogs, would you?
你可不想自己的臉被狗吃了吧？
If you die before me, I'll visit you as often as I can.
如果你比我先死，我會經常來看你的
I promise.
我保證
I think we should leave right now.
我覺得我們該走了
The three of us coming here instead of
我們三個人一起來
two or four is very dangerous.
而不是兩個或者四個一起來，這樣太危險了
Why didn't we think of that earlier?
怎麼沒早想到呢？
Highly likely the doctor will suspect us.
醫生很可能會懷疑我們的
I suggest that we leave the first chance we get.
我們還是盡早走吧
Right now, in fact.
現在就應該走
Don't be afraid.
別害怕
No one will suspect a thing.
沒人會懷疑的
I bet you weren't expecting this surprise.
你肯定沒料到這個驚喜吧
- Isn't it wonderful? - Yes, it is.
- 是不是很好？ - 確實
Still, I'd like a few days just to think it over, so that
但是我還想再考慮幾天
I could maybe have the surgery when we next come to the city.
要不等到下次進城的時候我再做手術吧？
What's there to think about?
有什麼好考慮的？
If it's better to see clearly or to be short-sighted? Is that it?
看得清楚總比近視好，對吧？
That's absurd, you know that.
沒什麼好顧慮的
Anyway, this doctor is the best there is.
這個醫生是業內最好的
And it's really very difficult to get an appointment.
很難預約
I called him months ago to get him to see you today.
我為了讓他今天見你，幾個月前就開始給他打電話了
She's blind.
她失明了
Thank you.
多謝
Throw down your knife and stand up.
把刀扔掉，站起來
Why did you have to blind me?
你為什麼一定到弄瞎我？
You could have blinded him.
為什麼不弄瞎他？
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我不知道你在說什麼
The drugs are messing with your head.
吃藥讓你頭腦不清醒了
If I were you, I would try and be a little braver about the whole thing.
如果我是你，我會勇敢一點
Now get up and give me your knife
站起來，把刀給我
or I'll hit you and take it by force.
否則我就不客氣了
- Here I come. - I swear I'm going to kill you.
- 我要過來了 - 我發誓會殺了你
Let go of my hair, you're hurting me.
放開我頭髮，你弄疼我了
Just think, that when someone goes blind
想想看，人失明後
one of the other senses
其它某個感官
is heightened.
就會變得敏銳
You could also catch a dog in the woods
你可以在樹林裏抓條狗
and train it to guide you.
然後訓練它給你導盲
Dogs can do that, you know.
狗可以導盲，你知道嗎
I'll help you catch a dog myself.
我會幫你抓狗
Now calm down, or I'm going to leave you here
安靜點，要不然我就把你扔在這兒
and I don't think you'll manage to find Meeting Point 2 on your own.
你一個人可找不到集合地點
Are you enjoying the view?
你在欣賞風景嗎？
Sure.
是啊
What happened to your hand?
你的手怎麼了？
I was cutting a tree branch with a knife and I cut myself by accident.
我砍樹枝的時候不小心傷到自己了
You look handsome today, did you get your hair cut?
你今天很帥，理髮了嗎？
Thank you.
謝謝你
No, I didn't get a haircut.
但是沒有
I'm going to get my hair cut today.
我準備今天去理髮
Look what I brought you.
看我給你帶了什麼
Oh, thank you so much. I'm so hungry, I'll eat it right away.
哦，真感謝你，我很餓，我現在就吃
It's a bigger flashlight.
是個大手電筒
Oh, I'm sorry.
噢，抱歉
It's so big, I thought it was a rabbit.
真是好大，我還以為是隻兔子
The biggest flashlight I've ever seen.
這是我見過最大的手電筒
Oh.
這樣啊
Are you ready for tonight?
你準備好今晚逃走了嗎？
Of course I am.
當然了
I want to tell you something but please don't be angry.
有件事我要告訴你，你一定不要生氣
OK. What's wrong?
好，怎麼了？
I can't see anything.
我看不到了
I'm blind.
我失明了
What do you mean?
什麼意思？
There's no point in lying to you, you'll find out sooner or later.
沒必要瞞著你，反正你早晚也會看出來的
Our leader blinded me in the city.
在城裏的時候，首領找人把我弄瞎了
She must have realised that I love you and you love me
她肯定發現我們相愛了
and that we were going to run away to the city together.
而且要一起逃到城裏去
I'm sorry.
對不起
You can't see at all?
你什麼也看不見了？
No, not at all.
對
And when you asked if I'd had my hair cut?
那怎麼問我有沒有理發？
I was just saying that
我那麼說
so you wouldn't realise that I can't see.
是因為不想讓你發現我失明了
I'm sorry.
對不起
Don't cry.
別哭
Crying will make your eyes hurt more.
眼睛會更疼的
We'll find a way.
我們會想出辦法的
What blood type are you?
你是什麼血型？
B.
B型
♪ From the first time I saw her, I knew she was the one
♪看到她的第一眼，我心便有所屬
♪ As she stared in my eyes and smiled
♪她凝望著我，微笑
♪ And her lips were the colour of roses
♪她的唇瓣艷似玫瑰
♪ That grew down the river all bloody and wild
♪順延河畔，血色奔放
Do you like berries? Blueberries, blackberries?
你喜歡吃莓果嗎，藍莓，黑莓？
- No, no. - Mm.
- 不，不喜歡 - 嗯
Can you play the piano?
你會彈鋼琴嗎？
No.
不會
Plastic cup.
塑料杯
That's right. Very good.
沒錯，很好
Do you speak German?
你會說德語嗎？
No.
不會
I could teach you German.
我可以教你
But it would take at least a year for you to be able to speak the basics,
但是想做到基礎交流至少得學一年
not fluently, so there's no point.
而且很不流暢，所以沒什麼意義
You know, German is one of the most difficult languages in the world to learn,
德語是世界上最難學的語言之一
because its grammar is very complicated.
因為德語語法很複雜
I brought you something.
我給你帶了點東西
It's a fish.
是一條魚
Oh.
噢
♪ On the second day, I brought her a flower
♪第二天，我為她獻上了花朵
♪ She was more beautiful than any woman I'd seen
♪她美貌勝過天僊
♪ And I said, Do you know where the wild roses grow
♪我說道，你可知野玫瑰在何處盛開
♪ So sweet and scarlet and free
♪甜美，猩紅，奔放
Kiwi.
獼猴桃
That's right, ten out of ten again.
很好，又全說對了
Can I give you a kiss?
我能吻你嗎？
I can't thank you enough for all the activities and games
謝謝你陪我做這些遊戲
and for keeping me company,
跟我待在一起
but you know we can't do that any more.
但是你也知道，我們不能這麼繼續下去了
Would you like to play another round of Touch-Guess-Think-Win?
你想再玩一輪你摸你猜嗎？
No, that's enough for today.
不了，今天足夠了
In any case, I've run out of things to test you with.
反正我也沒什麼東西可以用來考你了
Oh.
噢
Maybe tomorrow
也許明天吧
or one of these days.
或者最近哪天
Tomorrow morning?
明天早上可以嗎？
We'll see.
到時候再說吧
- Bye.
- 再見
Good afternoon.
下午好
How are you?
你好嗎？
Fine.
很好
I'm hungry.
我餓了
You haven't brought me a rabbit for days.
你很久都沒有送我兔子了
Or things for me to touch and guess.
也沒和我玩我摸我猜的遊戲
I've got good news.
我有好消息
I've had a great idea.
我想出了個好主意
Have you a minute?
你有時間聽嗎？
What kind of idea?
什麼主意？
I raise my left foot,
我抬起左腳
I bring my elbow to my knee and tap it twice.
用肘關節輕擊兩次膝蓋
I bring my foot to my knee and tap it three times.
用腳輕擊三次膝蓋
I lie face down, I kneel down.
我臉朝地面當下，再雙膝跪地
I touch my left cheek
我摸一下左臉
and then lie face up.
然後仰身躺下
Are you sure you're prepared to do that?
你確定你準備好那麼做了嗎？
Yes, of course I'm sure.
當然準備好了
I wouldn't propose it otherwise.
我想好了才告訴你的
When?
什麼時候動手？
Tomorrow.
明天
We should speed up a little.
我們得快點了
I can't go much faster.
我已經是最快了
The trousers are too tight. I'm sorry.
這條褲子太緊了，抱歉
It was dark and I couldn't see clearly.
當時天色很晚，我看不太清楚
And I didn't have time to try them on.
而且沒時間試
I'm sorry.
抱歉
Never mind.
沒關係
There's a bus coming.
有輛巴士往這邊來了
It was the hotel coach.
是酒店客車
They didn't see us.
他們沒發現我們
Profile.
側臉
Fingers.
手指
Elbows.
手肘
Would you like me to show you my belly?
你要看一下我的肚子嗎？
No.
不了
I, I remember your belly very well.
你的肚子，我記得很清楚
Smile.
笑一下
Can I have a knife and fork, please? Not a butter knife, a steak knife.
能幫我拿副刀叉嗎？不要黃油刀，要牛排刀
Certainly.
當然了
Thank you.
謝謝你
I'm going to do it with a knife.
我想用刀
Do you want me to come with you?
要我陪著你嗎？
I'd rather you didn't.
還是不了
Don't worry.
別擔心
It's strange at first, but then you get used to it.
開始會不習慣，但慢慢會習慣的
And your other senses are heightened -
之後你的其他感官會變敏銳
touch, for example, and hearing.
比如觸覺和聽覺
I know.
我知道
I won't be long.
我很快回來
Thank you very much.
非常感謝